Alcide, you sure know
how to treat a lady.
Alcide's employee is the
only person who can identify
whoever it was
that freed Russell.
It's a woman.
A female member
of the Authority released Russell.
Jesus, if you're out there,
can you give me a sign?
Lafayette!
It's called ifrit.
It means "the evil."
Eller, man, there's
no fire monster coming for us.
We killed those people
I saw it, Sergeant.
The ifrit.
Now we gotta pay.
It's coming for us.
The vampires will drain anyone
with even a drop of fairy blood
if they don't stay together.
We gotta get Sookie.
She might be better off
with the vampires.
No, no, no, no. One day they're
gonna turn on her.
I know it.
They will kill her
just like they did
your parents.
No, my parents
were killed in a flood.
Weren't they?
- Make yourself useful.
- So, basically, I'm your slave.
- Pretty much.
- My blood's not good enough for you?
Please!
Get off of him.
Shot down those poor people
in cold blood.
Is there anything else
you wanna tell me?
We're shifters.
Hey, shifter! Whoo!
We got him!
Emma, run!
- Wolves have been here.
- They come with Russell.
Took you long enough...
Hello, old friend. We've come
to finish what we started
Give it your best shot.
Alcide!
- Alcide!
- Sookie!
Alcide!
Bill!
Hmm.
Mmm.
You're just what
the doctor ordered,
my twee fairy vixen.
Yes, there is
that aspect of you