Don't show this text it may be used to insert hidden data
SubRip subtitles capability tester 1.3o by ale5000
Use VLC 1.1 or higher as reference for most things and MPC Home Cinema for others
This text should be blue
This text should be red
This text should be black
If you see this with the normal font, the player don't (fully) support font face
Hidden
This text should be small
This text should be normal
This text should be big
This should be an E with an accent: E
???
This text should be bold, italics and underline
This text should be small and green
This text should be small and red
This text should be big and brown
This line should be bold
This line should be italics
This line should be underline
This line should be strikethrough
Both lines
should be underline
>
It would be a good thing to
hide invalid html tags that are closed and show the text in them
but show un-closed invalid html tags
Show not opened tags
<
and also
hide invalid html tags with parameters that are closed and show the text in them
but show un-closed invalid html tags
This text should be showed underlined without problems also: 21,4
This shouldn't be underlined
This text should be in the normal position...
This text should NOT be in the normal position
Implementation is the same of the ASS tag
This text should be at the
top and horizontally centered
middle and horizontally centered
This text should be at the
bottom and horizontally centered
top and horizontally at the left
This text should be at the
middle and horizontally at the left
(The second position must be ignored)
This text should be at the
bottom and horizontally at the left
top and horizontally at the right
This text should be at the
middle and horizontally at the right
bottom and horizontally at the right
This could be the most difficult thing to implement
First text
Second, it shouldn't overlap first
Third, it should replace second
Fourth, it shouldn't overlap first and third
Fifth, it should replace third
Sixth, it shouldn't be
showed overlapped
TEXT 1 (bottom)
text 2
Hide these tags:
also hide these tags:
but show this:
\ N is a forced line break
\ h is a hard space
Normal spaces at the start and at the end of the line are trimmed while hard spaces are not trimmed.
The\hline\hwill\hnever\hbreak\hautomatically\hright\hbefore\hor\hafter\ha\hhard\hspace.\h:-D
\h\h\h\h\hA (05 hard spaces followed by a letter)
A (Normal  spaces followed by a letter)
A (No hard spaces followed by a letter)
\h\h\h\h\hA (05 hard spaces followed by a letter)
A (Normal  spaces followed by a letter)
A (No hard spaces followed by a letter)
Show this: \TEST and this: \-)
A letter followed by 05 hard spaces: A\h\h\h\h\h
A letter followed by normal  spaces: A
A letter followed by no hard spaces: A
05 hard  spaces between letters: A\h\h\h\h\hA
5 normal spaces between letters: A     A
\N^--Forced line break
Both line should be strikethrough,
yes.
Correctly closed tags
should be hidden.
It shouldn't be strikethrough,
not opened tag showed as text.
Not opened tag showed as text.
Three lines should be strikethrough,
yes.
Not closed tags showed as text
Both line should be strikethrough but
the wrong closing tag should be showed